aei-ideas.org 2019-06-26

# Terms Of Use

Collection of Information

When you register on the AEI website, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, e-mail address, and an account password). For certain services, such as book sales or donations, we also request credit card or other payment account information. AEI will collect information on this website only to the degree necessary to provide features and services, to complete online transactions, or to maintain the security of our network and maintain services as detailed below.

Cookie/Tracking Technology

When you visit AEI, we send one or more cookies — a small file containing a string of characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some web features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

The AEI website uses Analytics tracking code to support Display Advertising, specifically Remarketing & Google Analytics Demographics Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising Interest Reporting using [Google’s Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads).

This website server does not currently respond to the DNT signal, but you can enable DNT=on within your browser settings, and this will also opt-out of Remarketing and behavioural ads. Additionally, You may opt-out of all tracking by installing a [browser plug-in](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

Distribution of Information

AEI only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of AEI in the following limited circumstances:

We provide such information to other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; or(d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property, or safety of AEI, its users, or the public as required or permitted by law.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular article. Such information does not identify you individually.

Privacy Contact Information

For any issues related to AEI’s Privacy Policy, please contact [webmaster@aei.org](mailto:webmaster@aei.org) by e-mail or call 202-862-5800 and ask to speak to the webmaster.

Commitment to Data Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage, and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to AEI employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

AEI’s Participation in Amazon’s Associates Program

AEI is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.com.
